Guide to the International Association for Cultural Freedom Records 1941-1978
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Files
  - Subseries II: Correspondence and Subject Files, 1967-1978
    - Sub-subseries 3: "C"
      - Cercle pour la Liberte de la Culture-Lyon, 1970-1971 (Box 321, Folder 4)
      - Cercle pour la Liberte de la Culture-Lyon, 1971-1972 (Box 321, Folder 5)
      - Cercle pour la Liberte de la Culture-Lyon, 1972-1974 (Box 321, Folder 6)
      - Chenu, Roselyne, 1969-1971 (Box 322, Folder 1)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1968-1970 (Box 322, Folder 2)
      - China Quarterly, the, 1966 (Box 322, Folder 3)
      - China Quarterly, the, 1966-1967 (Box 322, Folder 4)
      - China Quarterly, the, 1968-1969 (Box 322, Folder 5)
      - China Quarterly, the, 1970-1972 (Box 322, Folder 6)
      - Cini Foundation, 1977 (Box 322, Folder 7)
      - Committee on Spain, 1967 (Box 322, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Spain, 1967-1977 (Box 322, Folder 9)
      - Committee on Spain, 1968-1971 (Box 322, Folder 10)
      - Committee on Spain, 1972 (Box 322, Folder 11)
      - Committee on Spain, 1972-1974 (Box 322, Folder 12)
      - Committee on Spain, 1973 (Box 323, Folder 1)
      - Committee on Spain, undated (Box 323, Folder 2)
      - Comptroller's Office, 1964-1966 (Box 323, Folder 3)
      - Comptroller's Office, 1967 (Box 323, Folder 4)
      - Congress for Cultural Freedom Publications, 1967 (Box 323, Folder 5)
      - Congress for Cultural Freedom Publications, 1974-1976 (Box 323, Folder 6)
      - Congress for Cultural Freedom Publications, 1974-1976 (Box 324, Folder 1)
      - Congress News, 1968 (Box 324, Folder 2)
      - Cook, Mercer, 1967 (Box 324, Folder 3)
      - Cosio Villegas, Daniel, 1967-1969 (Box 324, Folder 4)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1967-1969 (Box 324, Folder 5)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1970 (Box 324, Folder 6)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1967-1972 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Sub-subseries 4: "D"
      - Daedalus, 1967-1969 (Box 324, Folder 8)
      - Davis, Angela, 1969 (Box 325, Folder 1)
      - Dillon, Douglas, 1969 (Box 325, Folder 2)
      - Dillon, Wilton, 1965-1973 (Box 325, Folder 3)
      - Director General, 1974-1977 (Box 325, Folder 4)
      - Dissent, 1963-1967 (Box 325, Folder 5)
      - Doty, Paul, 1968-1977 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      - Doty, Paul, 1969-1973 (Box 325, Folder 7)
      - Duerdon, Dennis, 1965-1969 (Box 325, Folder 8)
      - Duffy, Joseph, 1973-1975 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 5: "E"
      - Eastern Europe, 1967-1970 (Box 325, Folder 10)
      - Editors' Meeting, 1969-1970 (Box 325, Folder 11)
      - Emmanuel, Pierre, 1962-1967 (Box 325, Folder 12)
      - Encounter, 1967-1969 (Box 326, Folder 1)
      - Encounter, 1970 (Box 326, Folder 2)
      - Encounter, 1971 (Box 326, Folder 3)
      - Encounter, 1971-1972 (Box 326, Folder 4)
      - Encounter, 1972 (Box 326, Folder 5)
      - Encounter, 1973-1974 (Box 326, Folder 6)
      - Encounter, 1975-1979 (Box 326, Folder 7)
      - Encounter, Tony Robinson, Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 326, Folder 8)
      - Entralgo, Pedro Lain, 1965 (Box 327, Folder 1)
      - Entralgo, Pedro Lain, 1968-1970 (Box 327, Folder 2)
      - Entralgo, Pedro Lain, 1971-1976 (Box 327, Folder 3)
      - Entralgo, Pedro Lain Clippings, 1966 (Box 327, Folder 4)
      - Entralgo, Pedro Lain Clippings, 1966 (Box 327, Folder 5)
      - Esthetique de L'Espace, 1969 (Box 327, Folder 6)
      - Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 327, Folder 7)
      - Executive Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 327, Folder 8)
      - Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 328, Folder 1)
      - Executive Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 328, Folder 2)
      - Executive Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 328, Folder 3)
      - Executive Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 328, Folder 4)
      - Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 328, Folder 5)
      - Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries 6: "F"
      - Farfield Foundation, 1957-1969 (Box 329, Folder 1)
      - Faust, Carlheinz, 1971-1972 (Box 329, Folder 2)
      - Fichera, Massimo, 1970 (Box 329, Folder 3)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 329, Folder 4)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 329, Folder 5)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 329, Folder 6)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 329, Folder 7)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 329, Folder 8)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 329, Folder 9)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 330, Folder 1)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 330, Folder 2)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 330, Folder 3)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 330, Folder 4)
      - Ford Foundation, Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 330, Folder 5)
      - Ford Foundation, Goodwin, Craufurd, 1974 (Box 330, Folder 5a)
      - Forum, Distribution Statistics, 1957-1968 (Box 330, Folder 6)
      - Forum, Information Services, 1962-1969 (Box 330, Folder 7)
      - Foundation pour un Estraide Europeene, 1967-1968 (Box 331, Folder 1)
      - Foundation pour un Estraide Europeene, 1969-1974 (Box 331, Folder 2)
      - Foundations, 1968-1969 (Box 331, Folder 3)
      - Foundations, 1968-1969 (Box 331, Folder 4)
      - Foundations, 1968-1969 (Box 331, Folder 5)
      - Foundation Clippings, 1963-1969 (Box 331, Folder 6)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, 1967-1968 (Box 331, Folder 7)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Bulgaria, 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Clippings and Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 332, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence "A," 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence "B-L," 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 4)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence "M-O," 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 5)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence "P-S," 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 6)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence "T-Z," 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 7)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence by Country "A-P," 1970 (Box 333, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Correspondence by Country "R-Z," 1970 (Box 333, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "A-B," 1968-1969 (Box 333, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "C-F," 1968-1969 (Box 333, Folder 4)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "G-J," 1968-1969 (Box 333, Folder 5)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "K-L," 1968-1969 (Box 333, Folder 6)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "M-P," 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "P-R," 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "S-V," 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Czechoslovakia Correspondence "W-Z," 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 4)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, East Germany, 1969 (Box 334, Folder 5)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Greece, 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 6)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Haiti, 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 7)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Hungary, 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 8)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Israel, 1969 (Box 334, Folder 9)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Mexico 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 10)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Pakistan, 1970 (Box 334, Folder 11)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Pakistan, 1970 (Box 335, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Pakistan, 1970-1971 (Box 335, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Pakistan, 1972 (Box 335, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Pakistan, 1972-1973 (Box 335, Folder 4)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Poland Correspondence "A-B," 1968-1969 (Box 335, Folder 5)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Poland Correspondence "C-K," 1968-1969 (Box 335, Folder 6)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Poland Correspondence "L-R," 1968-1969 (Box 335, Folder 7)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Poland Correspondence "S," 1968-1969 (Box 336, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Poland Correspondence "T-Z," 1968-1969 (Box 336, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Poland, 1970 (Box 336, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Portugal, 1968-1969 (Box 336, Folder 4)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Register, undated (Box 336, Folder 5)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Reports, 1970 (Box 336, Folder 6)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Reports and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 336, Folder 7)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Reports, Clippings, Press Releases, 1962-1969 (Box 336, Folder 8)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Romania Correspondence "A-B," 1968-1969 (Box 336, Folder 9)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Romania Correspondence "C-P," 1968-1969 (Box 336, Folder 10)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Romania Correspondence "R-Z," 1968-1969 (Box 336, Folder 11)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Scholarships "A-L," 1965-1969 (Box 337, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Scholarships "M-Z," 1966-1969 (Box 337, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Spain, 1968-1969 (Box 337, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Intellectuals, Yugoslavia,1968 (Box 337, Folder 4)
      - Fyvel, T.R. 1950-1955 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Sub-subseries 7: "G"
      - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1967-1972 (Box 337, Folder 6)
      - Gaspard, Armand, 1967-1975 (Box 337, Folder 7)
      - General Assembly, 1950-1969 (Box 337, Folder 8)
      - General Assembly, 1967 (Box 337, Folder 9)
      - General Assembly, 1968 (Box 337, Folder 10)
      - General Assembly, 1968 (Box 337, Folder 11)
      - General Assembly, 1968-1969 (Box 338, Folder 1)
      - General Assembly, 1969 (Box 338, Folder 2)
      - General Assembly, 1969 (Box 338, Folder 3)
      - General Assembly, 1969-1972 (Box 338, Folder 4)
      - General Assembly, 1969-1975 (Box 338, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, "A," 1967-1971 (Box 338, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, "A," 1972-1976 (Box 338, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, "B," 1967-1968 (Box 338, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, "B," 1969-1971 (Box 339, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, "B," 1972-1975 (Box 339, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, "B," 1976-1978 (Box 339, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, "C," 1967-1968 (Box 339, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, "C," 1969-1970 (Box 339, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, "C," 1970-1973 (Box 339, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, "C," 1973-1974 (Box 339, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, "D," 1967-1976 (Box 339, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, "E," 1967-1974 (Box 339, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, "F," 1967-1969 (Box 340, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, "F," 1970-1977 (Box 340, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, "G," 1967-1969 (Box 340, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, "G," 1970-1976 (Box 340, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, "H," 1967-1972 (Box 340, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, "H," 1973-1976 (Box 340, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, "I," 1967-1973 (Box 340, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, "K," 1967-1976 (Box 340, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, "L," 1967-1974 (Box 341, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, "M," 1959-1967 (Box 341, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, "M," 1967-1970 (Box 341, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, "M," 1970-1974 (Box 341, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, "N," 1967-1975 (Box 341, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, "O," 1967-1976 (Box 341, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, "P," 1965-1969 (Box 341, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, "R," 1967-1968 (Box 341, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, "R," 1969-1973 (Box 341, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, "S," 1967 (Box 341, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence, "S," 1968-1970 (Box 341, Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence, "S," 1971-1975 (Box 341, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence, "T," 1967-1976 (Box 342, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, "U," 1967-1976 (Box 342, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, "V," 1967-1976 (Box 342, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, "W," 1967-1976 (Box 342, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, "W," 1973-1976 (Box 342, Folder 4a)
      - General Correspondence, "X,Y, Z," 1968-1970 (Box 342, Folder 5)
      - Germany, 1967-1976 (Box 342, Folder 6)
      - Germany, 1974 (Box 342, Folder 6a)
      - German Marshall Fund of the United States, 1976-1977 (Box 342, Folder 7)
      - German Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 1)
      - Germany-Hamburg, 1967-1968 (Box 343, Folder 2)
      - Germany-Hamburg, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 3)
      - Germany-Hamburg, 1970-1971 (Box 343, Folder 4)
      - Germany-Hamburg, 1972-1974 (Box 343, Folder 5)
      - Gewen, Barry, 1971-1972 (Box 343, Folder 6)
      - Giedroyc, Jerzy, 1965-1969 (Box 344, Folder 1)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1967 (Box 344, Folder 2)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 344, Folder 3)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 344, Folder 4)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1971 (Box 344, Folder 5)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1972 (Box 344, Folder 6)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1973 (Box 344, Folder 7)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 344, Folder 8)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-G," 1967 (Box 344, Folder 9)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "H-L," 1967 (Box 344, Folder 10)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "M-R," 1967 (Box 344, Folder 11)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "S-Z," 1967 (Box 344, Folder 12)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-C," 1967 (Box 345, Folder 1)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "D-I," 1967 (Box 345, Folder 2)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "J-M," 1967 (Box 345, Folder 3)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "N-Z," 1967 (Box 345, Folder 4)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-B," 1969 (Box 345, Folder 5)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "C-J," 1969 (Box 345, Folder 6)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "K-L," 1969 (Box 345, Folder 7)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "M-O," 1969 (Box 346, Folder 1)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "P-S," 1969 (Box 346, Folder 2)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-I," 1970 (Box 346, Folder 3)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "J-S," 1970 (Box 346, Folder 4)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "T-Z," 1970 (Box 346, Folder 5)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-H," 1971 (Box 346, Folder 6)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "I-R," 1971 (Box 346, Folder 7)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "S-Z," 1971 (Box 347, Folder 1)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-H," 1972 (Box 347, Folder 2)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "I-S," 1972 (Box 347, Folder 3)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "T-Z," 1972 (Box 347, Folder 4)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "A-J," 1973-1974 (Box 347, Folder 5)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "K-S," 1973-1974 (Box 347, Folder 6)
      - Goldstein, David Correspondence "T-Z," 1973-1974 (Box 347, Folder 7)
      - Goodwin, Michael, 1968-1970 (Box 347, Folder 8)
      - Goodwin, Michael Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 347, Folder 9)
      - Goodwin, Michael Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 348, Folder 1)
      - Goodwin, Michael Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 348, Folder 2)
      - Grasset, Dominique, 1968-1971 (Box 348, Folder 3)
      - Greece, 1968-1970 (Box 348, Folder 4)
      - Greece, 1971 (Box 348, Folder 5)
      - Greece, 1973-1974 (Box 348, Folder 6)
      - Greece-Epoches, 1962-1970 (Box 348, Folder 7)
      - Greece-Press Releases and Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box 348, Folder 8)
      - Greece-Siotis, Jean, 1968-1970 (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 8: "H"
      - Hall, Ivan, 1969-1970 (Box 348, Folder 10)
      - Hall, Ivan, 1971-1974 (Box 349, Folder 1)
      - Hartley, Anthony, 1963-1973 (Box 349, Folder 2)
      - Harvard University, 1968-1971 (Box 349, Folder 3)
      - Heaps, David, 1968-1973 (Box 349, Folder 4)
      - Huberman, Michael, 1970-1971 (Box 349, Folder 5)
      - Hunt, John Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 349, Folder 6)
      - Hunt, John- Hutchinson Publishing, 1963-1968 (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Sub-subseries 9: "I"
      - IACF, 1958-1974 (Box 349, Folder 8)
      - IACF, 1959-1978 (Box 349, Folder 9)
      - IACF, 1962-1971 (Box 349, Folder 10)
      - IACF, 1963-1973 (Box 349, Folder 11)
      - IACF, 1967 (Box 349, Folder 12)
      - IACF, 1968-1970 (Box 350, Folder 1)
      - IACF, 1971-1973 (Box 350, Folder 2)
      - IACF Program and Bulletin, 1968 (Box 350, Folder 3)
      - IACF Solicitations for Employment, 1971-1973 (Box 350, Folder 4)
      - IACF Solicitations for Employment, 1973-1975 (Box 350, Folder 5)
      - IACF Solicitations for Employment, 1975-1976 (Box 350, Folder 6)
      - Iberian Program, 1973-1976 (Box 350, Folder 7)
      - IBI, 1970 (Box 350, Folder 8)
      - ICFU, Comparative Study of University Legislation [1/2], 1974-1977 (Box 350a, Folder 1)
      - ICFU, Comparative Study of University Legislation [2/2], 1977 (Box 350a, Folder 2)
      - ICFU, Continental University Laws, 1977 (Box 350a, Folder 3)
      - ICFU, "The Flight of Teaching," 1964 (Box 350a, Folder 4)
      - ICFU, Italian University Report, undated (Box 350a, Folder 5)
      - ICFU, Italian University Report, undated (Box 350a, Folder 6)
      - ICFU, "Some Facts and Figures on the Migration of Talent and Skills," 1967 (Box 350a, Folder 7)
      - ILO, 1969 (Box 350a, Folder 8)
      - India, 1967-1969 (Box 350a, Folder 9)
      - India, 1968 (Box 350a, Folder 10)
      - India, 1970-1971 (Box 351, Folder 1)
      - India, 1972 (Box 351, Folder 2)
      - India, 1972-1976 (Box 351, Folder 3)
      - India, Bombay, 1967 (Box 351, Folder 4)
      - India, Bombay, 1967 (Box 351, Folder 5)
      - India, Bombay, 1968 (Box 352, Folder 1)
      - India, Bombay, 1968 (Box 352, Folder 2)
      - India, Bombay, 1969 (Box 352, Folder 3)
      - India, Bombay, 1969-1970 (Box 352, Folder 4)
      - India, Bombay, 1970 (Box 352, Folder 5)
      - India, Bombay, 1970-1973 (Box 352, Folder 6)
      - India, Bombay, 1974-1975 (Box 353, Folder 1)
      - India, Bombay, Shah, A. B., 1976 (Box 353, Folder 2)
      - India, Bombay, Shah, A. B., 1977-1979 (Box 353, Folder 3)
      - India, Calcutta, Sinha, 1968-1969 (Box 353, Folder 4)
      - India, Center for Indian Writers, 1968-1969 (Box 353, Folder 5)
      - India, New Delhi, Rao, 1969-1970 (Box 353, Folder 6)
      - India, New Delhi, Sinha, 1968-1969 (Box 353, Folder 7)
      - Indonesia, 1968-1978 (Box 353, Folder 8)
      - Indonesia, Awjong, Budinam, 1968-1975 (Box 353, Folder 9)
      - Indonesia, Awjong, Budinam, 1972-1974 (Box 354, Folder 1)
      - Indonesia, Lubis, Mochtar, 1967-1971 (Box 354, Folder 2)
      - Indonesia, Lubis, Mochtar, 1972-1978 (Box 354, Folder 3)
      - Indonesia, Soedjatmoko, Sushil, 1967-1973 (Box 354, Folder 4)
      - International Council for Education Development, 1974 (Box 354, Folder 5)
      - International PEN Club, 1968-1971 (Box 354, Folder 6)
      - International PEN Club, 1969-1974 (Box 354, Folder 7)
      - Irish University Press, 1972 (Box 355, Folder 1)
      - Italy, 1964-1974 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Sub-subseries 10: "J"
      - Japan, 1966-1967 (Box 355, Folder 3)
      - Japan, 1968-1970 (Box 355, Folder 4)
      - Japan, 1971-1973 (Box 355, Folder 5)
      - Japan, 1974-1976 (Box 355, Folder 6)
      - Japan, Ishihara, Hoki, 1967 (Box 355, Folder 7)
      - Japan, Ishihara, Hoki, 1968-1969 (Box 355, Folder 8)
      - Japan, Ishihara, Hoki, 1970-1971 (Box 356, Folder 1)
      - Japan, Ishihara, Hoki, 1972-1976 (Box 356, Folder 2)
      - Jargy, Simone, 1967-1970 (Box 356, Folder 3)
      - Japan, Matsuo, M. and Okita Saburo, 1970-1975 (Box 356, Folder 4)
      - Jelenski, Constantine, Johnson Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 356, Folder 5)
      - Jelenski, Constantine, Scholarships, 1966-1970 (Box 356, Folder 6)
      - Job Applications, 1967-1972 (Box 356, Folder 7)
      - Job Applications, 1967-1972 (Box 356, Folder 8)
      - Josselson, Michael Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 11: "K"
      - Kaiser, Karl, 1972-1973 (Box 356, Folder 10)
      - Kaiser, Karl, 1973-1976 (Box 356, Folder 11)
      - Kallenbach, Zgymut, 1967-1970 (Box 357, Folder 1)
      - Kats, Ivan, 1967-1975 (Box 357, Folder 2)
      - Kelman, Steve, 1970-1973 (Box 357, Folder 3)
      - Kennan, George, 1967-1969 (Box 357, Folder 4)
      - Koestler, Arthur, 1959-1970 (Box 357, Folder 5)
      - Kolskowski, Leszek, 1969-1970 (Box 357, Folder 6)
      - Korea, 1967-1968 (Box 357, Folder 7)
      - Korea, 1967-1969 (Box 357, Folder 8)
      - Kraus, Walter, 1968-1970 (Box 357, Folder 9)
      - Kristol, Irving, 1962-1968 (Box 357, Folder 10)
      - Krygier, Richard, 1967-1973 (Box 357, Folder 11)
      - Krygier, Richard, 1974-1978 (Box 357, Folder 12)
      - Kwapong, A.A., 1967-1968 (Box 357, Folder 13)
      - Kwapong, A.A., 1970-1975 (Box 357, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries 12: "L"
      - Labdez, Leopold, 1967-1968 (Box 358, Folder 1)
      - Labdez, Leopold, 1968 (Box 358, Folder 2)
      - Labdez, Leopold, 1969 (Box 358, Folder 3)
      - Lambert, Galerie, 1967-1969 (Box 358, Folder 4)
      - Laqueur, Walter, 1967-1968 (Box 358, Folder 5)
      - Latin American Institute of International Relations Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 358, Folder 6)
      - Latin American Institute of International Relations Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 358, Folder 7)
      - Legal Correspondence and Documents-Publication Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 359, Folder 1)
      - Legal Correspondence and Documents-United Kingdom, 1968-1969 (Box 359, Folder 2)
      - Legal Correspondence and Documents-United Kingdom, 1970-1971 (Box 359, Folder 3)
      - Legal Correspondence and Documents-United States, 1968 (Box 359, Folder 4)
      - Lilly Endowment, 1973-1974 (Box 359, Folder 5)
      - Lilly Endowment, 1974-1976 (Box 359, Folder 6)
      - Lilly Endowment, 1977-1979 (Box 359, Folder 7)
      - Littauer Foundation, 1971-1976 (Box 359a, Folder 1)
      - Loble, Eugen, 1968-1970 (Box 359a, Folder 2)
    - Sub-subseries 13: "M"
      - Malaysia, 1961-1962 (Box 359a, Folder 3)
      - Malaysia-Lim Teck-ghee Project, 1974-1978 [1/2] (Box 359a, Folder 4)
      - Malaysia-Lim Teck-ghee Project, 1974-1978 [2/2] (Box 360, Folder 1)
      - Manshel, Warren, 1969-1970 (Box 360, Folder 2)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1976-1977 (Box 360, Folder 2a)
      - Maximov, Vladimir, 1967-1972 (Box 360, Folder 3)
      - Mehta, Asoka, 1967-1969 (Box 360, Folder 4)
      - Mindlin, Murray, 1967-1970 (Box 360, Folder 5)
      - Minerva, 1969 (Box 360, Folder 6)
      - Minerva, 1969-1970 (Box 360, Folder 7)
      - Minerva, 1970-1971 (Box 360, Folder 8)
      - Minerva, 1972-1973 (Box 361, Folder 1)
      - Minerva, 1973-1974 (Box 361, Folder 2)
      - Ministere de L'Education Nationale, 1968 (Box 361, Folder 3)
      - Monat, Der, 1968 (Box 361, Folder 4)
      - Monat, Der, 1967-1968 (Box 361, Folder 5)
      - Monat, Der, 1969 (Box 361, Folder 6)
      - Monat, Der, 1969-1970 (Box 361, Folder 7)
      - Monat, Der, 1970 (Box 362, Folder 1)
      - Monat, Der, 1970 (Box 362, Folder 2)
      - Monat, Der, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 3)
      - Monat, Der, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 4)
      - Monat, Der, 1971-1972 (Box 362, Folder 5)
      - Monat, Der, 1972-1975 (Box 362, Folder 6)
      - Montellier, 1963-1967 (Box 363, Folder 1)
      - Moroccan Mediterranean Studies, 1963-1967 (Box 363, Folder 2)
      - Moroccan Mediterranean Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 363, Folder 3)